[
    {
        "question": "Full form of JS is ____________?",
        "optionA": "JavaScript",
        "optionB": "Java Servelet",
        "optionC": "Java Server",
        "optionD": "JSON Script",
        "answer": "JavaScript"
    },

    {
        "question": "What does JavaScript supports?",
        "optionA": "Web Scripting",
        "optionB": "Object Oriented Programming",
        "optionC": "Game Programming",
        "optionD": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },

    {
        "question": "Which of these are introduced in ES6?",
        "optionA": "var",
        "optionB": "for loop",
        "optionC": "let and const",
        "optionD": "map()",
        "answer": "let and const"
    },

    {
        "question": "Function calling itself is called as______________?",
        "optionA": "Recursion",
        "optionB": "Normal function call",
        "optionC": "Function defination",
        "optionD": "Constructor",
        "answer": "Recursion"
    },

    {
        "question": "Lambda concept is a part of____________?",
        "optionA": "OOP ",
        "optionB": "Functional Programming",
        "optionC": "Arrow function",
        "optionD": "Looping",
        "answer": "Functional Programming"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is Filter used for?",
        "optionA": "Getting the elements of object which are satisfying any perticular condition.",
        "optionB": "Remove all array elements",
        "optionC": "Find bugs of the code",
        "optionD": "It is used as an option of looping.",
        "answer": "Getting the elements of object which are satisfying any perticular condition."
    },

    {
        "question": "var causes problem of___________?",
        "optionA": "datatype of variable",
        "optionB": "Does not create any problem",
        "optionC": "hoisting",
        "optionD": "both option one and three",
        "answer": "hoisting"
    },

    {
        "question": "ReactJS is a library of__________?",
        "optionA": "Java",
        "optionB": "JavaScript",
        "optionC": "Python",
        "optionD": "AngularJS",
        "answer": "JavaScript"
    },

    {
        "question": "What is the use of spread operator?",
        "optionA": "Working on same object instead of creating it's copy to optimize memory.",
        "optionB": "Making a copy of the selected object",
        "optionC": "Splitting an object into different variables.",
        "optionD": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Making a copy of the selected object"
    },

    {
        "question": "ReactJs was introduced in___________?",
        "optionA": "2010",
        "optionB": "2011",
        "optionC": "2012",
        "optionD": "2013",
        "answer": "2013"
    }
]